girlsoutwest.com 2018-06-04

# GirlsOutWest - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our website, a Boutique Media ("Boutique") product and/or service ("we" "our" or "us"). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this policy explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of the personally identifiable information you submit on our online and mobile websites, services, and applications ("Site" or "Sites"). For certain products and/or services, there may be additional notices about information practices and choices. Please read those additional privacy disclosures to understand how they apply to you.

We encourage you to contact an attorney of your own choosing and at your own expense in the event that you do not understand any of the terms contained in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with anything contained in this Privacy Policy then please cease and desist from using any of our Sites, products and/or services immediately. 

**OUR PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES ARE PROVIDED SOLELY TO ADULTS OVER THE AGE OF EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR THE AGE OF MAJORITY IN THE JURISDICTION WHICH YOU ARE UTILIZING ANY OF OUR PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES. CERTAIN PORTIONS OF OUR PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES MAY CONTAIN CONTENT CONSIDERED OFFENSIVE TO SOME, AND ARE INACCESSIBLE TO INDIVIDUALS UNTER THE AGE OF EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR THE AGE OF MAJORITY IN THE JURISDICTION WHICH YOU ARE UTILIZING ANY OF OUR PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES. FOR THOSE PORTIONS OF OUR PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES THAT MAY BE ACCESSIBLE TO INDIVIDUALS UNDER THE AGE OF EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR THE AGE OF MAJORITY IN THE JURISDICTION WHICH YOU ARE UTIZLING ANY OF OUR PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVICES, SUCH AS ANY OF OUR SITES' HOMEPAGES AND OTHER AREAS PRESENTING NON-OFFENSIVE CONTENT, WE HAVE NO INTENTION OF COLLECTING ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFABLE INFORMATION. PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR THE AGE OF MAJORITY IN THE JURISDICTION WHICH YOU ARE UTILIZING ANY OF OUR PRODUCTS AND/OR SERVIFCES SHOULD NOT SUBMIT ANY INFORMATION TO ANY OF OUR SITES. IF A MINOR HAS PROVIDED US WITH ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, A PARENT OR GUARDIAN OF THAT MINOR SHOULD CONTACT US AT THE EMAIL ADDRESS LISTED BELOW IMMEDIATELY.**

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary contained in this Privacy Policy, we make no representations or warranties of any kind whatsoever for information that you publish on any of our Sites, regardless of whether any such information is published voluntarily or involuntarily. Our Sites may contain a social networking component and you are utilizing our Sites with a full understanding and assumption of risk related to any and all information that you publish. 

  1. **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Registration and account information collected.** At some of our Sites, you can register to order products and/or services, become a member, read user reviews, enter contests, vote in polls, rate products and/or services, or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our electronic newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. In the course of using our Sites, we may ask you to create an account or complete an application by providing us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you, as well as to administer your account. The types of personally identifiable information that you provide as part of your account may include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card and billing information, and other information that you provide to us.

**Information from other sources.** We may, on occasion and in our sole and absolute discretion, combine information we receive online with outside records and use such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Social media.** You can also engage with our content and other offerings, such as videos, and applications, on or through third-party social media sites, plug-ins and applications. You may also choose to link your account with us to third party social media sites. When you link your account or engage with our content on or through third party social media sites, services, plug-ins, or applications, you may allow us to have ongoing access to certain information from your social media account. We may also receive non-personally identifiable information from your interaction with our content. 

When you provide information to a Site from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like: (i) give you exclusive content, (ii) personalize your online experience with us within and outside our Sites, and (iii) contact you through the social media sites or directly with the latest news, special offerings, and rewards. By providing such information, you consent to the use of the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

If you post information or content, such as by posting photos, commenting on a blog, or participating in online forums or communities at our Sites, or when you interact with our Sites through social media sites, plug-ins or other applications, depending on your privacy settings, this information may become public on the Internet. You expressly understand that we cannot prevent further use of this information. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social media sites. For more information about how you can customize your privacy settings and how third party social media sites handle your personally identifiable information, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy policies and terms of use. We make no warranties or representations of any kind whatsoever regarding how third party social media sites handle information posted through your account. Additionally, we make no warranties or representations of any kind whatsoever regarding the security of any information or content that you publish on any of the Sites. 

**Information collection from mobile devices.** If you access our Sites, on your mobile telephone or other mobile device, we also may collect your unique device identifier and mobile device IP address, as well as information about your device's operating system, mobile carrier, and mobile Internet browsers, your precise location information, and other information described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Providing requested information.** In some cases, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to order products, and services, or otherwise participate in the Site's offerings. 

**Technical and usage information.** We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you use our Sites such as but not limited to, the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider or mobile carrier, IP address, and certain usage information. 

  2. **HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION**

**Providing our products and services.** We use the information we collect about you to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to provide, personalize, and improve our offerings and to offer you other products, programs or services from us and our affiliates, business partners, and selected third parties that we believe may be of interest to you. 

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services. 

If you choose to submit content for publication, we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us on our Sites, the Internet, or elsewhere. Any content that you submit for publication shall immediately and irrevocably become our sole and exclusive property. 

**Communications.** We use information about you to communicate with you, including but not limited to: to notify you when you have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our user agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, to confirm purchases you have made through our Sites, or to contact you about your account with us. You may also choose to receive push notifications from us on your mobile device.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them invitations, gifts, cards, or other content on your behalf or through our Sites. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer products, programs, or services to them.

**Mobile Device Data Usage.** When you access our Sites on a mobile device, we may use the information collected for any of the purpose whatsoever so long as it complies with the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

**Use of non-personally identifiable information.** We use aggregate information about our users and non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design, functionality and content of our Sites and to enable us to personalize your experience with our Sites and offerings. We use this information to (i) provide, maintain, personalize, protect, improve, and develop our products, programs, and services and to operate our business, (ii) to analyze usage and performance of our Sites, and (iii) for us and our affiliates, business partners, and selected third parties to offer you products, programs, or services. 

  3. **INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

**Legal and law enforcement purposes.** We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, including but not limited to court orders and subpoenas, or in response to a law enforcement agency's request. We also may disclose such information to third parties in connection with fraud detection, and prevention activities or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of any of our terms of use or other policies, to protect our rights and the rights of others, and as otherwise required by law. 

You understand and agree that we maintain the option, in our sole and absolute discretion, to inform you of any disclosure of your personally identifiable information for legal and law enforcement purposes. 

**Change of control.** We may transfer any information about you in the event of a business transaction, such as if we or one of our business units or our relevant assets are acquired by, sold to, or merged with another company. 

**Our Vendors and service providers.** Our agents, employees and contractors may have access to personally identifiable information to help carry out the services they are performing for us. 

**Affiliates and other third parties.** We may disclose personally identifiable information about you to companies whose practices are not covered by this Privacy Policy. 

We may also share such information with business partners and third parties, such other marketers, publishers, retailers, participatory databases and non-profit organizations, that want to market products or services to you. 

**Linked third-party sites.** Some of our Sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. You should consult the other sites' privacy policies before submitting any information, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. We make no representations or warranties as to any content located on any linked sites and you hereby assume all risks associated with visiting said linked sites. 

**Sponsors and co-promotions.** We sometimes may offer content or programs that are sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the activity. We have no control over these third parties' use of this information.

**Advertisement servers.** At some of our Sites, reputable third parties may present or serve advertisements, provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and site analytics, and assist with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit, or set their own cookies. The use of these technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this Privacy Policy. They may also obtain information about other applications that you have downloaded to your mobile device, the mobile websites you visit, and other information about you or your device in order to help analyze and serve anonymous targeted advertising on the Site and elsewhere. 

  4. **YOUR CHOICES**

**Marketing Communications.** We provide you with an opportunity to express your preferences with respect to receiving certain marketing communications from us or from unaffiliated third parties. If you ever decide in the future that you would like to update these preferences, (i) you may log into your account if you have created an account with us at one of our Sites to adjust your settings, (ii) you may follow the "unsubscribe" instructions provided in any marketing email you receive from us, or (iii) you may send us an email at annie@girlsoutwest.com and we will edit your preferences accordingly. If you previously chose to receive push notifications on your mobile device from us but no longer wish to receive them, you can manage your preferences either through your device or app settings, depending on the type of device.

**Uninstalling a Mobile Application.** If you no longer wish to have any information collected by the Site, you may uninstall the application by using the standard uninstall processes available on your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. We make no representation of any kind as to the accessibility or stability of your wireless network and/or cellular service provider. 

  5. **COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNICAL INFORMATION**

**Cookies and Web beacons.** We, and our affiliates, third party service providers, and our business partners may send "cookies" to your computer or use similar technologies to enhance your online experience at our Sites. "Cookies" are files that can identify you as a unique customer and store your personal preferences as well as technical information. Cookies manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through us and/or other networks or sites. Cookies can either be persistent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser).

Some of our Sites may use locally stored objects (sometimes referred to as "Flash cookies") to provide certain content, such as video on demand, video clips, or animation. Adobe's Flash player and similar applications use this technology to remember settings, preferences, and usage similar to browser cookies. Flash cookies are not managed through your web browser, but you can access your Flash management tools from Adobe's web site.

We may also use "Web beacons" that monitor your use of our Sites. Web beacons are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a Web page for the purpose of transferring data, such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the Web beacon appears, the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the Web beacon appears, the time the page containing the Web beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the Web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. 

When corresponding with you via HTML capable email, Web beacons let us know whether you received and opened our email.

On their own, cookies or Web beacons do not contain or reveal any personally identifiable information. However, if you choose to furnish personally identifiable information, this information can be linked to the data stored in the cookies/Web beacons.

**Managing cookies and Web beacons.** By accepting this Privacy Policy, you specifically agree to our use of cookies and Web beacons as described herein. You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other Web site. Additionally, by setting your Web browser to display HTML emails as text only, you may be able to prevent the use of some Web beacons. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. However, certain areas of our Sites can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content or Site features. 

  6. **SECURITY**

We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures designed to safeguard the information we collect online at the Sites. Despite the reasonable security measure that we have created, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be used or disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

  7. **INFORMATION UPDATES AND/OR CORRECTIONS**

To access the personally identifiable information that our Sites have collected about you online from the pages on which this Privacy Policy is posted, to correct factual errors in such information, or to update your interests, preferences or other portions of your user profile, please log into your account if you have created one with us or send an email to annie@girlsoutwest.com.

To help protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

  8. **CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third-party company to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for our direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request will not be processed if it does not include your name and email address, the URL for the website you visited, and a return address. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year. Please email your request to annie@girlsoutwest.com.

  9. **PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and provide such amendments to you by posting a revised version on our Site. If the revised version includes a substantial change, we will provide you with Thirty (30) days' notice prior to the effectiveness thereof by posting notice of the change in a prominent place on the Site, such as presenting to you a click-through page immediately following your account login. Otherwise, in the case of insubstantial changes, the revised version will be effective at the time we post it. In any event, we will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most changes will be minor. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its Last Modified date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

  10. **CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or its implementation you may contact us at: annie@girlsoutwest.com.

  11. **HEADINGS**

Descriptive headings are for convenience only and shall not control or affect the meaning or construction of any provision of this Privacy Policy.
